Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- China College Files, Series IV
  - West China Union University
    - Correspondence
      - North, William R., 1926 (Box 289, Folder 4550)
      - Peat, J.F., 1926 (Box 289, Folder 4551)
      - Peterson, Robert A., 1938-1939 (Box 289, Folder 4551)
      - Phelps, Dryden L., 1928-1945 (Box 289, Folder 4552)
      - Pilcher, R.F., 1926 (Box 290, Folder 4553)
      - Priest, Elsie, 1940-1942 (Box 290, Folder 4553)
      - Rape, C.B., 1926-1927 (Box 290, Folder 4553)
      - Reisner, John H., 1926-1927 (Box 290, Folder 4553)
      - Robertson, H.D., 1935-1945 (Box 290, Folder 4554-4561)
      - Robertson, Marjorie, 1935-1941 (Box 290, Folder 4562-4564)
      - Sadler, Sir Michael E., 1930 (Box 290, Folder 4565)
      - Sawyer, Myra L., 1937-1938 (Box 290, Folder 4565)
      - Sewell, William G., 1934-1942 (Box 290, Folder 4566-4568)
      - Silcock, Harry T., 1935-1936 (Box 291, Folder 4569, 4570)
      - Simkin, Robert L., 1918-1943 (Box 291, Folder 4571)
      - Small, Walter, 1928 (Box 291, Folder 4571)
      - Small, William, 1941-1945 (Box 291, Folder 4572-4574)
      - Song, C.T., 1926 (Box 291, Folder 4575)
      - Soper, Sam H., 1926 (Box 291, Folder 4575)
      - Sparling, George W., 1926-1944 (Box 291, Folder 4576-4579)
      - Spooner, Roy C., 1938-1944 (Box 291, Folder 4580-4582)
      - Starrett, C.G., 1926-1936 (Box 291, Folder 4583)
      - Stuart, James L., 1926 (Box 291, Folder 4583)
      - Stubbs, Clifford M., 1928-1941 (Box 291, Folder 4583)
      - Taylor, Joseph, 1926-1927 (Box 291, Folder 4584)
      - Taylor, W.R., 1931 (Box 291, Folder 4584)
      - Tu, Shu-tung, 1942-1943 (Box 291, Folder 4584)
      - United Church of Canada, 1926-1945 (Box 292, Folder 4585-4592)
      - United Church of Canada, Women's Missionary Society, 1928-1939 (Box 292, Folder 4593)
      - Vaux, George, 1916-1923 (Box 292, Folder 4594)
      - Wallace, E.W., 1926-1927 (Box 292, Folder 4595)
      - Wang, Wallace, 1940-1945 (Box 292, Folder 4595)
      - Ward, Annie L., 1941 (Box 292, Folder 4595)
      - Ward, Ralph, 1926-1937 (Box 292, Folder 4595)
      - Wesleyan University, 1925-1937 (Box 292, Folder 4596)
      - West China Union Theological College, 1942-1943 (Box 292, Folder 4597)
      - Wilford, E.C., 1926, 1940 (Box 292, Folder 4597)
      - Yard, James M., 1926-1927 (Box 292, Folder 4598, 4599)
      - Yard, James M. (articles by), n.d. (Box 292, Folder 4600)
      - Yost, John, 1926 (Box 292, Folder 4601)
      - re. Youth Corps building, 1943-1944 (Box 292, Folder 4601)
    - Financial records
      - Reports on examination of accounts, 1927, 1928 (Box 293, Folder 4602)
      - Re. special gifts, 1926-1942 (Box 293, Folder 4603)
      - Miscellaneous, 1911-1946 (Box 293, Folder 4604-4608)
      - Ledger, 1926-1957 (Box 293, Folder 4609)
      - Ledger, 1944-1957 (Box 294, Folder 4610)
      - Transfer book, 1929-1950 (Box 295, Folder 4611)
    - Periodical Publications
      - WCUU News Bulletin, 1946-1948 (Box 296, Folder 4612, 4613)
      - College of Science Newsletter, 1940-1942 (Box 296, Folder 4614)
      - Journal of the West China Border Research Society, 1923, 1939, 1940 (Box 296, Folder 4615)
      - Studia Serica -- Journal of the Chinese Cultural Studies Research Institute, 1940 (Box 296, Folder 4616)
    - Publicity/reports
      - Publicity/reports, 1907-1933 (Box 296, Folder 4617-4622)
      - Publicity/reports, 1934-1950,n.d. (Box 297, Folder 4623-4630)
      - Publicity/reports: Chinese language (Box 297, Folder 4631)
  - Yenching University
    - Administrative
      - Re. charter, 1889-1929 (Box 298, Folder 4632)
      - Charter and amendments (see: oversize material), 1929, 1937 (Box 298, Folder 4633)
      - Re. constitution, by-laws, organization, 1929,n.d. (Box 298, Folder 4634)
      - Re. name of University, 1918, 1924, 1925 (Box 298, Folder 4635)
      - Re. Registration, 1925-1934 (Box 298, Folder 4636)
      - Predecessors: North China College, 1898 (Box 298, Folder 4637)
      - Predecessors: North China Union Women's College, 1915-1919 (Box 298, Folder 4638, 4639)
      - Predecessors: Peking University (Methodist): Brochure (Box 298, Folder 4640)
      - Predecessors: Peking University (Methodist): President's Report, 1912 (Box 298, Folder 4640)
      - Predecessors: Peking University (Methodist): Re. Student Volunteer Band, 1912, 1910 (Box 298, Folder 4640)
      - Predecessors: Peking University (Methodist) Minutes (bound volume), 1890-1914 (Box 298, Folder 4641)
      - Predecessors: Peking University (Methodist) Minutes, 1915 (Box 298, Folder 4642)
      - Union Committee on Constitution of the Federated Peking University, 1914 (Box 298, Folder 4643)
      - Board of Trustees of Yenching University (known in English as Peking University until 1928) Lists of members, 1917-1929 (Box 298, Folder 4644)
      - Board of Trustees of Yenching University: Index to minutes, 1916-1921 (Box 298, Folder 4645)
      - Board of Trustees of Yenching University: Index to minutes (bound volume), 1916-1929 (Box 298, Folder 4646)
      - Board of Trust. of Yen. Univ.: Minutes, 1916-1917 Apr (Box 298, Folder 4647)
      - Board of Trustees of Yenching University: Minutes, 1917 May-1929 Apr (Box 299, Folder 4648-4659)
      - Board of Trustees of Yenching University: Minutes, 1929 May-1940 (Box 300, Folder 4660-4670)
      - Board of Trustees of Yenching University: Minutes, 1941-1946,n.d. (Box 301, Folder 4671-4673)
      - Yenching University Committee of the UBCCC, 1945-1955 (Box 301, Folder 4674, 4675)
      - Yenching University Committee of the UBCHEA, 1956-1957 (Box 301, Folder 4676)
      - American Advisory Council, 1933 (Box 301, Folder 4677)
      - Index for minutes of Yenching College Committee, 1921-1935 (Box 301, Folder 4678)
      - Yenching College Committee of the Trustees of Peking University, 1921-1923 (Box 301, Folder 4679)
      - Yenching College Committee of the Trustees of Peking University (duplicates), 1921-1926 (Box 301, Folder 4680)
      - Yenching College Committee of the Trustees of Peking University, 1924-1928 Apr (Box 301, Folder 4681)
      - Committee of the Trustees of Yenching University for Yenching College for Women, 1928 Sep-1942 (Box 301, Folder 4682, 4683)
      - Yenching Women's College Committee of the UBCCC, 1946-1955 (Box 302, Folder 4684, 4685)
      - Yenching Women's College Committee of the UBCHEA, 1956-1957 (Box 302, Folder 4686)
      - Yenching College for Women: Administrative Committee, 1922-1941 (Box 302, Folder 4687)
      - Board of Managers, 1916-1939, 1947, 1948 (Box 302, Folder 4688-4694)
      - Board of Directors, 1942-1945 (Box 302, Folder 4695)
      - Administrative Committee, 1946 (Box 302, Folder 4696)
      - Board of Managers: Grounds and Building Committee, 1919-1931 (Box 302, Folder 4697-4701)
      - Conference on Postwar Rehabilitation, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 4702)
      - Annual reports to New York State Department of Education, 1917-1943, 1948 (Box 303, Folder 4703-4705)
      - Annual reports of President and Deans to Board of Managers, 1917-1943 (Box 303, Folder 4706-4712)
      - Annual reports of President and Deans to Board of Managers, 1944-1946, 1948 (Box 304, Folder 4713)
      - Annual reports of treasurers and controllers to Board Managers, 1930-1948 (Box 304, Folder 4714)
      - Reports and letters of President to Board of Trustees, 1925-1947 (Box 304, Folder 4715, 4716)
      - Proposed amalgamation with Shantung Christian University, 1922 (Box 304, Folder 4717)
      - Re. Yenching in Chengtu; incl. minutes of various committees, 1942-1944 (Box 304, Folder 4718)
      - Re. Buildings, campus, property, 1915-1947,n.d. (Box 304, Folder 4719-4721)
      - Blueprints, architectural drawings (For additional blueprints and architectural drawings, see: Oversize material)
      - Bashford Administration Building, Berry Memorial Library (Box 305, Folder 4722)
      - Chapel, Dining Hall, Recitation Building, School of Religion, Science Building (Box 305, Folder 4723)
      - Hospital and infirmary (Box 305, Folder 4725)
      - Lakefront dormitory group (Box 305, Folder 4726, 4727)
      - Practice school buildings (Box 305, Folder 4728)
      - President's residence (Box 305, Folder 4729)
      - Residences (Box 305, Folder 4730, 4731)
      - Scranton-Luce Social Island Warner Gymnasium (Box 306, Folder 4732)
      - Water tower and system (Box 306, Folder 4733)
      - Wiant Memorial Residence (Box 306, Folder 4734)
      - Women's College (Box 306, Folder 4735-4737)
      - Maps and campus plans (Box 306, Folder 4738)
      - Maps and campus plans (Box 307, Folder 4739-4743)
    - Academic
      - Course announcements, 1920-1948 (Box 308, Folder 4744-4747)
      - Directories, 1923-1936 (Box 308, Folder 4748-4751)
      - Directories, 1937-1944 (Box 309, Folder 4752, 4753)
      - General and entrance information bulletins, 1946, 1948,n.d. (Box 309, Folder 4754-4756)
      - Guidebooks for students, 1930-1936 (Box 309, Folder 4757)
      - re. Formal opening of University, 1929 (Box 309, Folder 4758)
      - re. Formal re-opening of University at Chengtu, 1942 (Box 309, Folder 4759)
      - Programs: Convocations and baccalaureate services, 1923-1938 (Box 309, Folder 4760)
      - Programs and articles re: Drama and music events, 1925-1944 (Box 309, Folder 4761)
      - Statistics re. student body and faculty, 1920-1950,n.d. (Box 309, Folder 4762)
      - re. Student body: Descriptions of activities; student statements re. Japanese invasion of Mukdon, 1931, 1925-1948 (Box 310, Folder 4763, 4764)
      - re. Student body: Religious life -- Yenta Christian Fellowship, 1926-1941,n.d. (Box 310, Folder 4765-4768)
      - re. Student body: Religious life -- misc., 1923-1950,n.d. (Box 310, Folder 4769-4771)
      - re. Student body:Transcript for Lin I, Diploma for Wang T'ung (see: Oversize material), 1941 (Box 310, Folder 4772)
      - re. Alumni: Lists and Alumni Association activities, 1923-1931 (Box 310, Folder 4773)
      - re. Alumni: Lists and Alumni Association activities, 1933-1949 (Box 311, Folder 4774-4776)
      - re. Alumni: Questionnaires, 1947 (Box 311, Folder 4777)
      - Lists of alumni and former faculty in the USA and Canada; Alumni Association activities, 1951-1973 (Box 311, Folder 4778)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Lists, 1922-1948 (Box 311, Folder 4779)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Biographical info: Frame, Alice Browne; Gamewell, Frank; Lew, Timothy Ting-fang; Lowry, H. H.; Luce, Henry Winters; Miner, Luella; Ogilvie, Charles; Porter, Lucius C.; Stuart, J. Leighton; Shih, Yu Tang (and others) (Box 311, Folder 4780)
      - re. Faculty and staff: conferences and retreats, 1923-1933, 1947 (Box 311, Folder 4782)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Meetings of faculty committees and organizations, 1922-1937, 1946 (Box 311, Folder 4783)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Missions code numbers, 1936-1940 (Box 311, Folder 4784)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Re. Yenching "internee community", 1943 (Box 311, Folder 4784)
      - re. Faculty and staff: List of Gripsholm repatriates, 1942 (Box 311, Folder 4784)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Noices from Chancellor's and President's offices, 1936-1940 (Box 311, Folder 4785)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Questionnaires, 1947, 1948 (Box 311, Folder 4786)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Miscellaneous, 1922-1940, n.d. (Box 312, Folder 4790)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Adolph, William, 1946 (Box 312, Folder 4791)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Boynton, Grace, 1943 (Box 312, Folder 4791)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Chang Tung-sun, 1943 (Box 312, Folder 4791)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Chao, T. C., 1939 (Box 312, Folder 4791)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Cheng Lin-chuang, 1937 (Box 312, Folder 4791)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Dean, Sam (Box 312, Folder 4791)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Dickinson, Jean, 1924 (Box 312, Folder 4792)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Gamewell, Frank D., 1900 (Box 312, Folder 4792)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Hague, Hilda, 1931 (Box 312, Folder 4792)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Hsia Yun, 1943 (Box 312, Folder 4792)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Hsu, Leonard, 1927, 1932 (Box 312, Folder 4793)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Hsu, Yung-san (Box 312, Folder 4793)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Hung, William, 1930, 1934 (Box 312, Folder 4794)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Kramer, Martha, 1944 (Box 312, Folder 4794)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Lamb, Jefferson, 1932 (Box 312, Folder 4795)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Lew, Timothy Ting-fang, 1923-1934 (Box 312, Folder 4796)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Li An-che, 1939 (Box 312, Folder 4796)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Liang, Hubert, 1937, 1938, 1946 (Box 312, Folder 4796)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Liu Cheng-chao, 1940 (Box 313, Folder 4797)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Lowenthal, Rudolf, 1939 (Box 313, Folder 4797)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Lu Hui-ching, 1948, n.d. (Box 313, Folder 4797)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Lu Kuang-mien, 1932 (Box 313, Folder 4797)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Mei, Y. P., 1939, 1943 (Box 313, Folder 4798)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Milam, Ava, 1947 (Box 313, Folder 4798)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Miner, Luella (Box 313, Folder 4798)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Speer, Margaret B., 1944 (Box 313, Folder 4798)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Stewart, Mrs. Maxwell, 1928 (Box 313, Folder 4798)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Stuart, J. Leighton, 1924-1941, n.d. (Box 313, Folder 4799-4801)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Tayler, J. B., 1924-1937 (Box 313, Folder 4802)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Ting Han-po, 1936-1940 (Box 313, Folder 4803)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Tsia, Stephen, 1946 (Box 313, Folder 4803)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Wee, K. A., 1937 (Box 313, Folder 4804)
      - re. Faculty and staff: Publications/writings: Anonymous and lists, 1931-1947, n.d. (Box 313, Folder 4804)
      - Colleges of Arts and Sciences: General bulletins and reports, 1919, 1922, 1925 (Box 313, Folder 4805, 4806)
      - College of Arts and Letters: General bulletins and reports, 1929-1932, 1934 (Box 314, Folder 4807-4809)
      - College of Natural Sciences: General bulletins and reports, 1929-1934, 1942, 1949 (Box 314, Folder 4810-4812)
      - College of Applied Social Sciences: General bulletins and reports, 1928-1930 (Box 314, Folder 4813)
      - College of Public Affairs: General bulletins and reports, 1930-1947,n.d. (Box 314, Folder 4814-4815B)
      - Women's College: General bulletins and reports, 1923-1945,n.d. (Box 314, Folder 4816)
      - Peking Union Medical College, 1921 (Box 315, Folder 4817)
      - School of Religion (See also: Correspondence), 1922-1935,n.d. (Box 315, Folder 4818-4820)
      - School of Chinese Studies (joint project with North China Union Language School), 1925-1927 (Box 315, Folder 4821)
      - Research School of Chinese Studies (Harvard-Yenching Institute) (See also: Series VI; Harvard-Yenching Institute), 1925-1944 (Box 315, Folder 4822-4824)
      - Proposed School of Applied Economics, 1928 (Box 315, Folder 4825)
      - Graduate Division, 1927, 1929-1932 (Box 315, Folder 4826, 4827)
      - Graduate Yuan, 1937-1940 (Box 315, Folder 4828)
      - Bureau of Industry/Bureau of Economic Experiment and Service/North China Industrial Service Union, 1920-1933 (Box 316, Folder 4829)
      - Department of Agriculture, 1923-1931,n.d. (Box 316, Folder 4830-4832)
      - Department of Education, 1920-1939,n.d. (Box 316, Folder 4833-4835)
      - Department of Journalism, 1923-1938,n.d. (Box 316, Folder 4836-4838)
      - Department of Leather Manufacture/Tanning, 1923, 1925 (Box 316, Folder 4839)
      - Department of Music, n.d. (Box 316, Folder 4839)
      - Department of Physical Education, 1928-1944,n.d. (Box 316, Folder 4840)
      - Department of Political Science, 1926-1928 (Box 317, Folder 4841)
      - Department of Sociology and Social Work, 1919-1932, 1943 (Box 317, Folder 4842-4846)
      - Craftwork Industrial Center (Box 317, Folder 4847)
      - re. Library, ca.1923-1941,n.d. (Box 317, Folder 4848)
      - re. Correlated programs and cooperation, 1928-1935 (Box 317, Folder 4849)
      - re. Famine relief, 1921-1935,n.d. (Box 317, Folder 4850, 4851)
      - re. Rural reconstruction and relief projects, 1936, 1938,n.d. (Box 317, Folder 4852)
      - University-related songs, n.d. (Box 317, Folder 4853)
      - University motto, n.d. (Box 317, Folder 4853)
      - Miscellaneous, 1917-1945,n.d. (Box 317, Folder 4854)
      - University banners, n.d. (Box 318, Folder 4855)
    - Correspondence
      - Adolph, William H., 1921-1947 (Box 319, Folder 4856-4858)
      - Ament, William S., 1938 (Box 319, Folder 4859)
      - American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions, 1916-1945 (Box 319, Folder 4860-4866)
      - American Home Economics Association, 1944 (Box 319, Folder 4867)
      - American Society of Newspaper Editors, 1928-1931 (Box 319, Folder 4867)
      - Amoy, National University of, 1944-1945 (Box 319, Folder 4868)
      - Andrews, Kate R., 1928-1941 (Box 319, Folder 4868)
      - Angle, William M., 1942 (Box 319, Folder 4869)
      - Arnold, Marie L., 1942-1945 (Box 319, Folder 4869)
      - Atherton Trust Funds, 1928-1946 (Box 319, Folder 4869)
      - Avann, Orpha C., 1922-1946 (Box 319, Folder 4870-4872)
      - Bailie, Joseph, 1919-1925 (Box 319, Folder 4873-4875)
      - Baker, John Earl, 1928 (Box 320, Folder 4876)
      - Band, William, 1932-1945 (Box 320, Folder 4877, 4878)
      - Barber, George G., 1931-1936 (Box 320, Folder 4879)
      - Barbour, George B., 1921-1945 (Box 320, Folder 4880)
      - Barrows, H.K., 1935-1937 (Box 320, Folder 4881)
      - Bartlett, Robert M., 1924-1931 (Box 320, Folder 4881)
      - re. Bashford Memorial Building, 1923-1927 (Box 320, Folder 4882)
      - Bent, Dora, 1932-1942 (Box 320, Folder 4883)
      - Bequest (anonymous), 1930 (Box 320, Folder 4883)
      - re. Berry Memorial Library, 1920-1933 (Box 320, Folder 4884, 4885)
      - Bevan, L.R.O., 1937-1942 (Box 320, Folder 4886)
      - Bigelow Foundation, 1943 (Box 320, Folder 4886)
      - Biggerstaff, Camilla and Knight, 1928-1944 (Box 320, Folder 4886)
      - Bill, Caroline E., 1931-1937 (Box 320, Folder 4887)
      - Blacker, Mr. and Mrs. R.R., 1924-1936 (Box 320, Folder 4887)
      - Blaine, Mrs. Emmons, 1932-1936 (Box 320, Folder 4887)
      - Blair, Mary Barbour, 1928-1949 (Box 320, Folder 4888-4890)
      - Blaisdell, Allen C., 1937 (Box 320, Folder 4891)
      - Bocker, L.M., 1922-1945 (Box 320, Folder 4891)
      - Bonnell Family, 1923-1929 (Box 320, Folder 4892)
      - Boring, Alice, 1922-1947 (Box 320, Folder 4893-4896)
      - Boring, Edwin G., 1942-1943 (Box 321, Folder 4897)
      - Bowman, Louis A., 1922-1940 (Box 321, Folder 4898)
      - re. Boxer indemnity, 1923-1924 (Box 321, Folder 4899)
      - Boyd, William and Corabel, 1924-1937 (Box 321, Folder 4900-4902)
      - Boynton, Edith, 1928-1930 (Box 321, Folder 4903)
      - Boynton, Grace, 1920-1956 (Box 321, Folder 4904-4909)
      - Brandt, Mary, 1936 (Box 321, Folder 4910)
      - Breece, Thomas E., 1941-1945 (Box 321, Folder 4910)
      - Britton, Roswell S., 1924 (Box 321, Folder 4910)
      - Bronson, Oliver H., 1922-1947 (Box 321, Folder 4911)
      - Brown, Alice Barlow, 1930 (Box 321, Folder 4911)
      - Brown, Arthur Judson (See: Presbyterian Church in the USA) (Box 321, Folder 4911)
      - Brown, Stuart F., 1938-1946 (Box 321, Folder 4911)
      - re. Buildings for women's college, 1923-1928 (Box 321, Folder 4912)
      - Burgess, John and Stella, 1943-1944 (Box 321, Folder 4913)
      - Burton, Margaret, 1932-1942 (Box 321, Folder 4913)
      - Burtt, Lucy M., 1930-1942 (Box 322, Folder 4914, 4915)
      - Cabot, Godfrey L., 1925-1946 (Box 322, Folder 4916)
      - Cadwallader, Isabella, 1933-1948 (Box 322, Folder 4917)
      - Cairns, D.S., 1927 (Box 322, Folder 4917)
      - Calder, Helen B., 1935-1945 (Box 322, Folder 4917)
      - California College in China, 1930-1941 (Box 322, Folder 4918)
      - Calvary Presbyterian Church, Cleveland, 1923 (Box 322, Folder 4918)
      - Candlin, George T., 1928 (Box 322, Folder 4919)
      - Cargin, W.M., 1928 (Box 322, Folder 4919)
      - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1931 (Box 322, Folder 4919)
      - Caskey, Herbert K., 1924-1927 (Box 322, Folder 4920)
      - Cavert, Twila Lytton, 1940 (Box 322, Folder 4920)
      - Chamberlain, Joseph P., 1931-1935 (Box 322, Folder 4921)
      - Chamberlain, Mary, 1928-1943 (Box 322, Folder 4921)
      - Chamberlain, Walter E., 1923-1928 (Box 322, Folder 4922, 4923)
      - Chambers of Commerce, 1931-1932 (Box 322, Folder 4924)
      - Chang, Hung-chun, 1927-1935 (Box 322, Folder 4925)
      - Chang, Ke (Sheng Jung), 1927-1930 (Box 322, Folder 4925)
      - Chang, Paul C., 1937-1938 (Box 322, Folder 4926)
      - Chang, Timothy, 1935 (Box 322, Folder 4926)
      - Chang, Wen-li, 1928-1930 (Box 322, Folder 4926)
      - Chang, Yin-tang, 1927, 1928 (Box 322, Folder 4926)
      - Chao Cheng-hsin, 1947 (Box 322, Folder 4926)
      - Chao, T.C., 1927-1941 (?) (Box 322, Folder 4927, 4928)
      - Char, Tin-yuke (Hsieh, Ting-yu), 1934-1947 (Box 322, Folder 4929)
      - Chen, Agnes, 1939-1948 (Box 323, Folder 4930)
      - Chen Chin-miao, 1941 (Box 323, Folder 4931)
      - Chen, Frances, 1932-1940 (Box 323, Folder 4931)
      - Chen, Gideon, 1933-1940 (Box 323, Folder 4931)
      - Ch'en, Hung-shun, 1941-1944 (Box 323, Folder 4932)
      - Chen, Kenneth and Chao-ying, 1935-1939 (Box 323, Folder 4933)
      - Chen, T.Y., 1927-1928 (Box 323, Folder 4933)
      - Chen, Yi-chen, 1945 (Box 323, Folder 4933)
      - Chen Yuan, 1926-1935 (Box 323, Folder 4933)
      - Cheney, Monona L., 1931-1943 (Box 323, Folder 4934)
      - Cheng, Andrew C.Y., 1920-1927 (Box 323, Folder 4935)
      - Chen, Ch'eng-k'un, 1939-1944 (Box 323, Folder 4935)
      - Chen, David, 1940 (Box 323, Folder 4936)
      - Cheng, Jason L.C., 1933 (Box 323, Folder 4936)
      - Cheng, Ronald Y.S., 1934 (Box 323, Folder 4936)
      - Chevalier, John B., 1931 (Box 323, Folder 4936)
      - Chiang, May-ling Soong, 1938-1941 (Box 323, Folder 4937)
      - The Chicago Tribune, 1928-1939 (Box 323, Folder 4938)
      - Child Welfare Association, 1928-1948 (Box 323, Folder 4939)
      - Chin, Ruth, 1944 (Box 323, Folder 4940)
      - China Educational Commission, 1921 (Box 323, Folder 4940)
      - China Medical Board, 1919-1927,n.d. (Box 323, Folder 4941)
      - Chinese Students Christian Association, 1936 (Box 323, Folder 4942)
      - Cho I-lai, 1930-1931 (Box 323, Folder 4942)
      - Chou Chi-hsien, 1944 (Box 323, Folder 4943)
      - Chou Ching-fu, 1921-1930 (Box 323, Folder 4943)
      - Chou Fu-chuan, 1921 (Box 323, Folder 4943)
      - Chou, Henry and Ruth, 1931-1940 (Box 323, Folder 4944)
      - Chou, Nien-tzu, 1940 (Box 323, Folder 4944)
      - Chou Shun-hsin, 1939-1942 (Box 323, Folder 4945)
      - Chou Tso-min, 1930 (Box 323, Folder 4945)
      - Chow, Lucy, 1940 (Box 323, Folder 4946)